was just like everything [music] else
humanity does. They have no [__]
clue. They have no respect. Now, I don't
want to videotape any of this. I just
want to tell them to go the [__] home.
Don't tell anybody about what you've
done because you have [__] up.
>> What the [__] is happening is happening.
>> A sacrilege.
>> You just really don't know.
>> There's no action to fix this. I'll just
let you see.
>> They're currently digging up what I
believe are burial sites.
>> Found this when you were building this.
>> Yeah.
that [music] were specifically buried in
a specific order for a specific reason.
What I feel is a mix of rage and
hostility and disgust.
This is extremely disrespectful what
they're doing here. I can feel it in my
soul.
Sadness all at once at the deepest
levels of my being. I'm kind of numb. If
you look in my eyes, you can feel me.
Those people over there can feel me from
sitting here. They can feel the disgust
welling out of me, flowing right into
them. And I just want to tell them to go
the [__] home. Don't tell anybody about
what you've done because you have [__]
up.
>> This is like the cave of wonder and
Aladdin. And the only one who can go in
there is somebody with pure intention
and heart. They don't know what these
things are. They don't know what they
do. It's just like everything else
humanity does. They [__] do [__] and
have no [__] clue. They have no
respect. They have no reverence. They
have no dignity.
>> Move over to that one. There's
[__] [music]
selling these things. I feel powerless
to stop it. I could. I'm telling you.
It's on Instagram to dumb asses in
Sedona so they can put them on their
[__] shelf and show their goddamn
friends.
And it's all because of money. The
devil's doing his job. This is meant to
[music] be found in a certain order and
assembled by a certain group of people
who have a certain frequency.
There's not a lot of us on planet Earth,
but I'm pretty sure I'm [__] one of
them. Now, I don't want to videotape any
of this. It's disrespectful.
You shouldn't videotape some things.
They shouldn't be captured like this,
and none of it should be sold. And I'm
surrounded by [__] who don't
have a goddamn clue.